{
    "subject": "resource/Martijn_de_Zwart",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Dutch_footballers",
    "human_readable": "Martijn de Zwart is about Dutch footballers.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9167914390563965,
            "question": "Is Martijn de Zwart a footballer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8169147372245789,
            "question": "Who is Martijn de Zwart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7434602975845337,
            "question": "Are there famous Dutch footballers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6931543946266174,
            "question": "What nationality are Dutch footballers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6588642597198486,
            "question": "Where might you find information about Dutch footballers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5393919944763184,
            "question": "What does Martijn de Zwart specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5213037133216858,
            "question": "What is the history of Dutch football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4837193787097931,
            "question": "What are some popular football leagues featuring Dutch players?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4182659387588501,
            "question": "Can you name any famous Dutch football teams?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11544491350650787,
            "question": "What makes a footballer successful?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Martijn de Zwart is about Dutch footballers.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2400_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any famous Dutch football teams?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2400_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular football leagues featuring Dutch players?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2400_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of Dutch football?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2400_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2400_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2400_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2400_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2400_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2400_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2400_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2400_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2400_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2400_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2400_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Martijn de Zwart, a Dutch footballer. They mention his career details and confirm that he plays as a goalkeeper for Quick Boys in the Netherlands, supporting the statement that he is about Dutch footballers."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}